

Maxime DE LA ROCHETERIE

- Développeur Web & Mobile Full Stack
- contact@maxdlr.com
- Lyon, France

in My Linkedin Profile

T +33614743706

www.maxdlr.com

Let me start off by saying that I am a 32 year old dad starting anew.
Before that idea I rocknrolled as a freelance motion designer for 10 years.
I've worked alone, in teams, for days, for nights, solved problems, made some, learned new softwares and skills every other day. I've adapted, managed, created and taught.
I'm sure all that will come in handy.

TECH SKILLS

LANGUAGES

PHP HTML MYSQL CSS JS

FRAMEWORKS

REACT.JS SYMFONY
DBEAVER BOOTSTRAP
GITHUB

ENVIRONMENTS
LINUX WINDOWS

FIGMA

BLENDER

ADOBE OFFICE

EDUCATION

Web & Mobile Developer (Titre RNCP Niveau 5)

Wild Code School 2023

3D & VFX Bachelor

Aries, Lyon 2014

SOFT SKILLS

Autonomy
Problem solving mindset
Detail oriented
Team member
Organization freak
Great dad

LANGUAGES

French - Mother tongue English - Bilingual

INTERESTS

Leather crafting Bike riding Video games Traveling

EXPERIENCE

2023 - present

Web & Mobile dev full-stack - Training @WildCodeSchool

- 27-02-2023 ---> 28-07-2023 | Intensive training
- Studying PHP oriented web coding/programming at Wild Code School. According to this->syllabus.
- Hoping to learn software development through more studies, or in-house, should the occasion arise.
- BamSystem Project. // 1st website done in 2 weeks. Space tourism agency with planet visits and spaceship rentals.

2014 - 2023

Freelance Motion Graphics Designer

- From 3D/VFX designer to onto Motion design over the years.
- · Self-taught.
- · New skills every other day.
- · Mostly remote work, adaptable, autonomy.
- Lots of in-house work, in teams, as lead and/or member.
- · VIP clients: Ubisoft, FTV, BBC, BMW, Fifa, Euronews, Arte

2018 - 2022

Adobe After Effects & Motion Design Instructor

- 3D & design schools, 5 year programs / 5 day programs
- · VIP schools: Eartsup, Brassart, Ynov, 3IS.
- · Teaching map, planning and writing programs.
- Team management
- · Class lesson content writing
- Team/Student Project management